弗兰克  我们会面的目的
The whole reason we do these meetings, Frank,
就是为从你那儿得到准确的信息
is so I can get accurate information from you.
我始终说票数会很胶着
I always said it was going to be close.
那为什么昨天我读到的报道
Then why did every article I read yesterday
都说领导集团相信法案会通过
say the leadership was confident the bill would pass?
您知道简宁・斯克斯基吗
Do you know Janine Skorsky?
她曾任《先驱报》驻白宫记者
She used to be the Herald's White House correspondent.
我记得简宁
I remember Janine.
她为头条网写了篇文章
She wrote an article for Slugline
报道了一份经核实的计票结果
reporting a verified vote count.
一旦被媒体拿到  那东西就满天飞了
Once the media got ahold of that, it went everywhere.
我不知道她哪弄到的数字
I don't know where she got that number.
或许是她编造的
Maybe she made it up.
是不是她编的不重要
It doesn't matter if she made it up.
外界认为民主党出现了分歧
The democrats seem divided.
领导集团就显得很无能
The leadership looks incompetent.
与财政预算和我们的教育法案相比
But compared to the the budget and our education act,
这不过是个小法案  先生
well, this was a minor bill, sir.
可它恰恰却受全国瞩目
That happened to be in the national spotlight,
这是你想要的
which is what you wanted.
计票我算错了
I got the count wrong.
这很罕见  但确实发生了
It rarely happens, but it happens.
令我担心的是  白宫方面的影响
What worries me is that the White House's influence
没能在国会给你支持
isn't translating into support on the hill.
琳达的参与没起到丝毫作用
Linda's involvement had no effect?
并不是这么回事  先生
I wouldn't say that that's the case, sir.
教育法案之争有没有带来
Did you sense any push-back, any fallout
什么阻力和影响
from the education battle?
先生  事实是我并未出席
Sir, the truth is I wasn't there.
我当时必须得去趟加州
I had to make a trip to California
为我儿子去见斯坦福的教务长
to meet the Provost of Stanford for my son.
我上周跟您提过
I told you about it last week.
这是我的主意  先生
It was my decision, sir.
我当时认定
I made a judgment call
没有她的帮助法案也能通过
that we could pass the bill without her help.
但事实是  这种差距甚微的投票
But, look, tight votes like this,
分析不出个所以然来
you can analyze them to death,
最终结果就是我们票数落后
but at the end of the day, we came up short.
这只归咎于我个人  绝非琳达的错
That's my fault, no one else's. Certainly not Linda's.
我当时就不该离开
I shouldn't have gone.
那场会面毫无成果
The meeting didn't even work.
你不是说他们会重新考虑
I thought you said they were reconsidering.
不  我今早收到一封邮件
No. I got an e-mail this morning.
他们决定不推翻招生办的决定
They decided not to overturn the admissions decision.
天呐  真是遗憾  琳达
Oh, Christ. I'm sorry, Linda.
今天不怎么顺利
Not a great day so far.
不过还是要谢谢你刚才为我打圆场
But I appreciate your covering for me in there.
或许琳达的噩运能变成我的机遇
There may be a way to turn Linda's bad luck into my good fortune.
不过首先我要解决组织内的背叛
But first I must deal with treason within the ranks...
那两个投反对票的叛徒
the two renegades who voted against the bill.
我绝不容忍背叛行为
I have zero tolerance for betrayal,
很快  他们就会永远记住这点
which they will soon indelibly learn.
我知道投票失利的原因
I know why you lost the vote.
有人去找了范德博格和艾布拉姆斯
Somebody got to Vanderburgh and Abrams.
雷米・丹顿
Remy Danton.
你妻子
Your wife.
我在他们两边都有联络人
I've got contacts on both their staffs.
他们三人见过一面
There was a meeting between the three of them.
我知道  我安排的
I know. I arranged it.
-她让他们投反对票  -不是这样
- She told them to vote no. - No, not true.
那两边的人怎么说法完全一致
Sources on two different staffs saying the exact same thing?
这完全没道理
That makes no sense.
我不是在跟你讲道理
I'm not telling you what makes sense,
我是在陈述事实
I'm telling you facts.
这可是个猛料  弗兰西斯
This is a juicy story, Francis.
卡莉绝对会喜欢
Carly will love it.
多数党党鞭的妻子在背后捅他刀子
The majority whip's wife stabs him in the back.
当心点  佐伊
Be careful, Zoe.
我在给你提供信息
I'm feeding you.
现在你该给我提供信息了
Now you have to feed me.
给我点更好的新闻
So give me something better.
回答我的问题
Are you going to answer my question?
她有没有那么做
Did she or didn't she?
快说  否则上帝保佑
Tell me now, or so help me God,
我会倾尽一生
I will make it my mission in life
毁掉你们的职业生涯
to not only destroy your careers,
碾碎你们努力博得的一切幸福与希望
but to obliterate all hope and happiness that you manage to cling to.
-她说我们可以  -在背后捅我刀子吗
- She said it would be okay... - To backstab me?
做我们认为对的事
To do what we thought was right.
那她的确让你们投反对票了
So she did tell you to vote no.
她说即使法案不通过也不是世界末日
She said it wouldn't be the end of the world if the bill failed.
这是她的原话
Those were her exact words.
这件事不许跟任何人说  明白了吗
You discuss this with no one. Is that understood?
没待在华盛顿为法案拉票你感到自责吗
Do you blame yourself for not being in Washington to secure the votes?
这么大的法案要靠团队合作
A bill this size is a team effort.
还有其他联署人呢
There are a lot of sponsors.
但你是主发起者  法案的负责人
But you were the chief sponsor and the bill manager.
话是不错
That's true.
那你不是该留在华盛顿吗
So shouldn't you have been in Washington?
我在竞选州长
I'm running for Governor.
我要履行对宾州人民的职责
I have a commitment to the people of my state.
你是否知道斯沃夫阵营
Are you aware that the Swofford campaign
今天放出新的宣传语
is putting out a new commercial today that says,
"如果彼得・罗素在国会都撑不下去
quote, "If Peter Russo can't follow through in congress,
他还能抵住酒精的诱惑吗"
can he follow through with sobriety?"
访问到此结束  非常感谢各位
That's all. Thank you very much.
-你不作出回应吗  -谢谢各位
- Do you want to comment? - Thanks, guys.
议员先生
Congressman!
我不过是说了你常说的  凭良心投票
All I said was what you always say... to vote their conscience.
你鼓动他们违抗我
You encouraged them to defy me.
我见过他们了  你要我...
I met with them. That's what you asked me...
不  你不是只见面了
No, that is not what you did.
我明确说了需要他们投赞成票
I specifically told you I needed them to vote yes on this bill.
根本毫无歧义
There was no room for interpretation.
你存心撒谎  不要再粉饰了  克莱尔
It's a deliberate lie, so don't try to sugarcoat it, Claire.
我需要雷米的帮助  你又不帮我
I needed Remy's help. You wouldn't offer any.
等下
Oh, wait.
你是为雷米这么做的
You did this for Remy?
不是  为我自己  我要把货从苏丹运出来
No. For myself. To get my shipment out of Sudan.
他施以了援手
He provided assistance.
以否决法案作为代价
In exchange for defeating the bill.
不  只是没有促成法案通过
No. In exchange for not helping it succeed.
不就是一回事吗
Which is the same goddamn thing.
你知不知道你危及了
Do you realize you have endangered
我们一直以来苦心经营的一切
everything that we have been working toward?
一切都安排好了啊  克莱尔
There was a timetable here, Claire.
直到最后一刻我们都得保持这股劲头
We needed strong momentum right up until the last minute.
你遇事不和我商量  我怎么依计划行事
I can't operate based on plans you haven't shared with me.
那你也该先问我一下
Then you should've asked me first.
不  我不会每次做决定
No, I'm not going to ask for your blessing
都征求你的意见  弗兰西斯
on every decision I make, Francis.
我们是一起做决定
We make decisions together.
我怎么没觉得
Yeah, well, it hasn't felt like that.
至少过去六个月不是这样
Not for the past six months.
我没觉得我们是在并肩作战
I don't feel as though I'm standing beside you.
有人知道这事  克莱尔
Other people know, Claire.
这可能成为我们的把柄
This could become a story about us.
而且是一竿子就能把人打死的事
And that's something you do not recover from.
-谁知道  -这种事永远洗刷不掉
- Who? - That's something that follows you for life.
谁知道
Who knows?
佐伊
Zoe.
你不是说她可以信任吗
I thought you said she could be trusted.
那我们之间的信任呢
What about our trust?
你无法控制她  是吧  弗兰西斯
You can't control her, can you, Francis?
你如果没撒谎  她就不是问题
She wouldn't have been a problem if you hadn't lied.
不  如果你没跟她上床
No, she wouldn't have been a problem
她才不是问题
if you hadn't dropped your pants.
你来我办公室  痛斥我一顿
And you come in here, to my office, and berate me
而实际上这都是你的错
when you're the one who's exposed us?
你休想把矛头指向我
Don't you try to turn this around on me.
我为你解雇了一半的员工
I fired half of my staff for us.
回绝了送上门的捐款
I have turned down donations for us.
起草了彼得的法案
I drafted Peter's bill for us.
搁置我自己的理想  去忙你的事
I diverted time and energy away from my goals for us.
好吧  我本不想这么说的
Okay, I don't wanna have to say this,
但你或许该听听
but maybe you need to hear it.
净水计划是重要
C.W.I. is important, yes,
但它根本比不上我们努力奋斗的目标
but it doesn't come close to what we are trying to accomplish.
你要认清这一点
You must see that!
我只是实事求是
I'm just being honest.
那就老实承认你利用了我
Then be honest about how you've been using me
就像你利用其他人
just like you use everybody else.
可从没说过会是这样
That was never part of the bargain.
是因为潮热[更年期症状]吗
Is it the hot flashes?
滚出去
Get out.
给我滚
回家再见
I'll see you back at the house.
我在去办公室的路上
I'm on my way to the office.
到那儿给你电话
Let me call you when I get there.
不  现在就谈
No, no. We need to talk now.
我知道你很生气  彼得
I know you're upset, Peter,
但那也没有用
but that's not going to achieve anything.
我不止生气  弗兰克
I am more than upset, Frank.
注意你的语气  我没心情
Change your tone. I'm in no mood.
-我不在乎  -再见  彼得
- I don't give a fuck! - Good-bye, Peter.
你挂我电话  就别怪我接下来去找谁
You hang up on me now, you're not gonna appreciate who I call next.
-你说什么  -我承诺给我的人民工作
- Excuse me? - I promised my people jobs.
你承诺会让这份法案通过
You promised me you could get this bill passed.
你食言了  但我不会
You failed on your promise. I'm not gonna fail on mine.
无论你想什么办法  把这问题解决掉
So however you need to fix it, you figure it out.
否则  我就把科佩尼科和科恩社论的事抖出来
Otherwise, I go public with Kapeniak and the Kern editorial.
你需要冷静
You need to cool down
仔细地考虑下刚才说的话
and think very carefully about what you just said.
你不明白  我不再怕你了  弗兰克
You don't understand. I'm not afraid of you anymore, Frank.
那你就大错特错了
Then you're misguided.
我的过去已经公开了
My past is out in the open.
你再也不能以此威胁我了
You don't hold that over my head anymore.
他们不知道所有事  彼得
They don't know everything, Peter.
你毁了我  就是毁你自己
You destroy me, you destroy yourself.
快解决
Fix it.
-你要我怎么做  -加快进度
- What do you want me to do? - We have to accelerate things.
是不是早了点
Isn't it too early?
离选举还有近两个月
It's almost two full months into the election.
这样白宫的审查能做得很充分
That gives the White House too much time to vet somebody.
彼得越界了
Peter's crossed the line.
我们为他建立自信  现在控制不住他了
We built up his confidence, and now we're losing control of him.
也许他只是在发脾气
Maybe he was just blowing off steam.
不  他主意已定  我们得马上行动
No. He's determined. We have to act now.
你那边准备妥当了吗
You have everything you need on your end?
给我时间地点就行
Give me a when and a where.
最好是社交场合
Some sort of social setting's preferable.
-还有吗  -我需要现金
- Anything else? - I'll need cash.
大概三千
About three grand.
明早放在你上层抽屉里
It'll be in your top drawer by tomorrow morning.
先生
Sir...
一旦这么做  就不能回头了
Once we do this, we're committed.
-我知道  -我无法预测他的反应
- Understood. - I can't predict how he's gonna react.
我不能忍受勒索
Well, I won't be blackmailed.
谁
Hello?
佐伊・巴恩斯
Zoe Barnes?
是的  你是谁
Yeah. Who is it?
克莱尔・安德伍德
Claire Underwood.
佐伊
Zoe?
很抱歉我没有按门铃
I apologize for not buzzing.
我在楼下时  正好有人进楼
Somebody was coming in the building when I was downstairs,
所以我就...
so I just figured...
有防火梯  不错啊
This is nice... fire escape.
你能别乱碰我的东西吗
Hey, could you please not go through my things?
对不起  我打扰到你了吗
Oh, I'm sorry. Am I intruding?
是啊
Yeah, actually. You are.
那我们真是彼此彼此了
Well, that makes it a two-way street, I suppose.
如果你是来惩罚我的
Okay, if you... if you came here to punish me...
好吧  我懂的
Fine. I get it.
真可惜
Such a shame,
你太天真了
how naive you are.
-我不天真  -是吗
- I'm not naive. - No?
我从一开始就知道一切  佐伊
I've known everything from the beginning, Zoe.
我和我丈夫之间无话不谈
My husband and I tell each other everything.
你不信我吗
Don't you believe me?
这里有蜘蛛让我抓吗
Is there a spider I can trap?
我不是来惩罚你  或是叫你停手
I'm not here to punish you or to tell you to stop.
我只是想让你睁大眼睛看清事实
I just thought I should open those big bright eyes.
我想你该走了
I think you should leave.
我想也是
I think I should too.
也许你没那么天真
Maybe you're not that naive.
换个小丫头连门都不敢开
A lesser woman wouldn't have opened the door.
到联合车站
Union Station, please.
我是克莱尔  现在不能接听你的电话
This is Claire. I'm unavailable to answer the phone,
如果你留了言
but if you leave a message,
我会尽快回复你
I'll be sure and get back to you shortly.
谢谢
Thank...
-喂  -佐伊
- Hello? - Zoe.
你不用轻手轻脚的
You don't have to tiptoe.
我以为你睡着了
I thought you fell asleep.
没有  在想工作的事
No. Just thinking about work.
我现在还没有料给你  很快就有了
I don't have anything for you yet. I will soon.
我知道
I know you will.
你愿意的话  可以在这里过夜
You can spend the night if you want.
还要早起开会
Early meetings.
那样就没时间回家换衣服了
Wouldn't have time to get home and change.
-你好像心神不宁  -烦心事太多
- You seem distracted. - I have a lot on my mind.
比如
Like what?
-工作的事  和你一样  -克莱尔呢
- Work, just like you. - No Claire?
或者她也算工作
Or maybe she qualifies as work.
她什么都没提吗
She didn't mention anything?
提什么
About...
你们不是无话不谈吗
I thought you didn't keep things from each other.
想说什么就说
Look, just say what you want to say.
她几个小时前来过
She came by here a few hours ago.
我们聊了一会儿
We had a nice little talk.
你走吧
Don't let me keep you.
你该回家休息一下
You should go home, get some rest.
代我向克莱尔问好
Tell Claire I said hi.
我是克莱尔  现在不能...
This is Claire. I'm unavailable to answer...
沃顿家的灯待会儿就要亮了
The lights in the Whartons' house will go on in a few moments.
他们总是6点45准时起床
They always get up precisely at quarter to 7:00,
如果克莱尔在这儿
which is just the time that Claire would be going for her run,
她就会这时去跑步
if she were here.
谁都不听话
Rebellion on all fronts...
克莱尔  佐伊  罗素
Claire, Zoe, Russo.
我不能失去决心
I must not lose my resolve.
我会继续向前
I will march forward,
即便我必须
even if I have to do so...
独自前行
alone.
说中了吧
See? Told ya.
早上好
Good morning.
你好  弗兰克
Hi, Frank.
-你好吗  -很好
- How are you? - I'm good.
-收到克莱尔的消息了吗  -嗯  她的短信
- Have you heard from Claire? - Yeah, I got her message.
-她感觉怎么样  -好多了
- How's she feeling? - A lot better.
很好  她说她下周前都没法来
Good. She said she'd be gone for the rest of the week.
-是流感吗  -差不多
- Is it the flu or something? - Something like that.
我就过来到她办公室拿点东西
I just came over to pick up a few things from her office.
-我可以找人送去的  -不  没事的
- I could've sent somebody over. - Oh, no. It's no big deal.
其实  我还想来请你帮个忙
In fact, I also came here to ask you a favor.
你念的斯坦福  对吧
You went to Stanford, correct?
-还致了告别辞  -对
- Valedictorian? - Yeah.
-你认识教务长吗  -沃伦・泰斯戴尔
- Do you know the provost? - Warren Tynsdale.
他让我组织募捐活动
He flies me out to do fund-raising events.
可能我是校友的杰出代表吧
Supposedly I'm the poster child for alumni.
让世界更美好
Making the world a better place.
那很好  这事很重要
Well, that is good, because this is important.
琳达・瓦斯奎兹  总统的幕僚长
Linda Vasquez, the President's chief of staff...
她的儿子鲁本递了申请
her son, Ruben, applied.
我希望你能打电话给泰斯戴尔
I'd love for you to get on the phone with Tynsdale
告诉他学校应该录取他
and tell him that they should accept him.
这...我从没推荐过别人
I don't know. I... I've never recommended anyone.
这样更好  更有分量
All the better. It'll carry more weight.
我能先见见鲁本吗
Can I meet Ruben first?
我其实不想让琳达知道
I would really prefer that Linda not know.
其实  最好让他们母子
In fact, it would be better if both she and Ruben
都以为他是因为出色而被录取
believed he got in on merit alone.
能帮我和克莱尔这个忙吗
Will you please do this favor for Claire and me?
也算帮了总统
And for the President.
谢谢
Thank you.
增加对比度
More contrast.
我们要捕捉他的面部轮廓
We need to catch the edge of his face.
重新剪裁吧  左边加四分之一英寸
Let's re-crop it. Bring it in a quarter of an inch on the left.
能去...
Would you...
有个克莱尔找你
Somebody named Claire?
雷米
Remy.
饿吗
You hungry?
我不吃猪肉
I don't eat pork.
什么时候的事
When did that happen?
开始给肉类加工业游说时
When we started lobbying for the meatpacking industry.
弗莱迪  给我半块肋排
Freddy, half a rack for me,
再给我朋友来点羽衣甘蓝
and some Collard Greens for my friend here.
不用了  我吃过午饭了
I'm good. I already ate lunch.
半块肋排马上就好
Half a rack coming up.
我一般不在这儿谈公事
I don't usually do business here.
这里是我的小秘密
This is my little secret.
希望你别说出去
I'd love it if we could keep it that way.
你不用担心我会带客户过来
I don't think you have to worry about me bringing clients by.
你好像很紧张  雷米
You seem tense, Remy.
流域法案的事你很生气吧
I assume you're upset about the watershed bill.
我不怪你  你只是在做本职工作
Not with you. You were just doing your job.
但我也得做好我的工作
But now I have to do mine.
我想建立合作关系
I'd like to propose a partnership.
我一向愿意合作  弗兰克
I'm always open to partnerships, Frank.
如果彼得・罗素支持天然气开采
If Peter Russo were a pro-natural gas candidate,
对桑科有多大的价值
how valuable would that be to Sancorp?
但流域法案反对开采
The watershed bill was anti-drilling.
彼得是支持就业  不是反对开采
Peter's pro-employment, not anti-drilling.
他只是想为选民创造更多就业机会
He just wants to bring employment to his people,
而桑科刚好在建设精炼厂
and Sancorp is building refineries.
但大多数都建在当地
Mostly on site.
你认为桑科会考虑
Do you think they would be open
在费城建厂吗
to considering Philadelphia?
我可以和他们谈谈  但不能保证
I can talk with them, but I can't make any promises.
我不需要保证  你就先去和罗素谈谈
Oh, I don't want any promises. Just engage with Russo.
描绘一下美好前景之类的
You know, give him a glimmer of good fortune.
来了  弗兰克
Frank, here you go.
闻闻这香味
Come on. Smell that.
真不想改主意吗
You sure you don't want to reconsider your stance on pork?
健脑食品啊  兄弟
Brain food, brother.
-我喜欢这地方  -每月850美金
- I love it. - 850.
能付得起吗
You can afford that?
没问题
Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
首末两月的租金已经付过了
First and last month are taken care of.
押金也付了
So is the security deposit.
用这笔钱买点家具吧
That's to buy some furniture.
我会还给你的  我保证
I'll pay you back. I promise.
不用了
It's not necessary.
不过我确实要请你帮个忙
But I do need you to do one thing for me.
-人们会觉得我是个伪君子  -你得增加就业
- I come across as a hypocrite. - You need jobs.
谁会在乎那些职位是怎么来的
Do you really care how you deliver them?
我先是主张加强对流域的管制
First, I advocate for more regulation for the watershed,
然后又去投奔开采业
then I cozy up to the drilling interests?
但天然气是大势所趋  彼得
Yeah, but natural gas is the future, Peter.
这一产业能在未来十年
This is an industry that could bring
给你家乡带来十万个工作岗位
100,000 jobs into your state over the next decade.
我和彼得想法一致  这样做有点出尔反尔
I agree with Peter. It seems like flip-flopping.
流域法案的流产要归咎于桑科的游说
Sancorp's lobbying efforts is why we lost the watershed bill.
但他们也会成为强大的盟友
But they can also be a very powerful ally.
我们的竞选口号是"崭新的开始"
Our message is a "Fresh start."
这么做会让人觉得你并没改变
This makes you look like business as usual.
这是政治
This is politics.
你可以抓住机会  也可能错过机会
There are seized opportunities and missed opportunities.
抓住这个机会  彼得
Seize this one, Peter.
桑科能保证在费城新建精炼厂吗
Sancorp can commit to building new refineries in Philly?
桑科能保证和你商讨此事
Sancorp will commit to discussing it with you.
-这可不够  -你让我解决问题
- I need more than that. - Look, you asked me to fix a problem.
我在24小时之内就给出了解决方案
I've come to you in less than 24 hours with a solution.
你能不能也做出让步呢
Can you meet me halfway?
第一步要怎么做
What would be the first step?
很好  还记得雷米・丹顿吗
All right. You remember Remy Danton?
得了吧  就是他牵头反对流域法案的
Oh, come on. He led the charge against the watershed bill.
我知道  但这不重要
I know. That's not the point.
麦克奈利癌症研究所也是他的大客户之一
One of his other big clients is the McNeally cancer institute.
他们今晚将举办一场宴会
They're having a big gala tonight...
鸡尾酒会  宴请捐款人
a cocktail party... for their donors.
雷米也会到场
Remy will be there.
我们在哈弗福德和格莱德文有活动...
We have events in Haverford and Gladwyne...
这件事更重要
Yeah, well, this is more important.
你明早还要跟匹兹堡当地的电台
You also have a radio interview tomorrow morning
做连线访谈  对吗
with a local Pittsburgh station?
-是的  -好吧
- Yes. - All right.
今晚和雷米谈谈
Meet with Remy tonight.
如果谈得顺利而且你也愿意
And if it goes well and if you're comfortable,
就在明早访谈的时候
tomorrow morning on the radio,
表示支持他们开采
you support their drilling efforts.
雷米已经向我保证  如果你这么做了
And Remy has assured me if you do that,
他会说服桑科跟我们合作
he can push Sancorp in the right direction.
取消明天的活动
Cancel the events tomorrow.
回费城去  尽力弥补损失
Head back to Philly, do some damage control.
-我明天下午就过去  -彼得
- I'll see you tomorrow afternoon. - Peter...
拜托
Please.
好吧
Okay.
我去打几个电话
I'm gonna go make some calls.
彼得  你跟她提过科佩尼科吗
Peter, have you mentioned anything to her about Kapeniak or...
没有  我没跟任何人说过
No. I haven't mentioned it to anybody.
好吧  明早斯坦普会过去
All right. Stamper will come by in the morning
向你说明要点
and brief you on the talking points.
这是什么时候拍的
When did you take this?
大概是早上七点
Oh, it was about 7:00 in the morning.
太阳刚出来
The sun had just come up.
你正在酣睡  就在这里
You were asleep... right here.
光线很完美
The light was perfect.
我情不自禁
I had no choice.
在这个公寓我一向睡得安稳
I always slept so well in this apartment.
这次要待多久
How long are you in town for?
我不知道
I don't know.
还没想好
I haven't decided.
你没带行李
You have no luggage.
这里的味道还是一样
It smells the same.
感觉也没变
Feels the same.
不在费城占有一席之地
I think Sancorp is missing out,
是桑科的损失
not having a significant presence in Philadelphia.
以大城市为中心是有好处
There are advantages to centralizing in a major urban center.
但也有缺点  商业地产的地价
But the disadvantages are commercial real estate prices,
缴城市税  铺设管道
city taxes, building a pipeline.
这些都耗资巨大
It's all very costly.
那就得从其他方面削减开支
So they'd have to reduce costs elsewhere.
-当然  -我能帮上什么忙
- Significantly. - How can I help with that?
开放全州土地
Statewide permitted-use zoning.
去除区划限制
No more conditional zoning.
地方政府阻碍了发展
The municipalities are slowing down development.
但这是宾州法律啊
That's the state legislature.
你要是支持开放土地
You come out in support of permitted use,
就能当选州长了
and you get elected Governor.
这能给立法机构造成压力
That'll put pressure on the legislature.
桑科很愿意在哈里斯堡[宾州首府]
Sancorp is very interested in having
结交一位有分量的朋友
a powerful friend in Harrisburg.
我的对手也支持开采
My opponent's pro-drilling.
但你的对手没说要在费城建精炼厂
Your opponent isn't asking for refineries in Philadelphia.
我们更喜欢靠得住的朋友
We prefer friends we can count on.
让你的客户明早7点45分收听WZPZ
Have your clients listen to WZPZ tomorrow at a quarter to 8:00.
是匹兹堡的电台
It's a Pittsburgh station.
聊得很愉快  议员先生
It's been a pleasure, Congressman.
希望能尽快再谈
I look forward to talking again soon.
有打火机吗
You got a light?
这可是癌症研究宴会
This is a cancer research event.
我知道  我也帮忙组织了啊
I know. I helped organize it.
-你在研究所工作  -不  是酒店
- You work for the institute? - No. The hotel.
他们让你在这儿抽烟
And they let you smoke here?
不  经理会杀了我的
No. The manager would kill me.
不过至少让你开口了
Well, at least it got you talking.
今晚很顺利吗  你看起来很高兴
Are you having a good night? You look happy.
是啊  很顺利
Uh, I am. I am. I'm having a great night.
-为什么  -刚刚收到了好消息
- Why? - I just got some very good news.
那得庆祝一下  你要喝什么
We should celebrate. What are you drinking?
其实我正打算走了
You know, I was just leaving, actually.
你还没问我叫什么呢
You haven't even asked my name yet.
-抱歉  但我得走了  -我叫瑞秋
- I apologize, but I have to go. - It's Rachel.
我不想失礼  但我明天还有个重要会议
I'm not trying to be rude, but I got a big meeting tomorrow.
那就别失礼  再待会儿
Then don't be rude. Just stay a few more minutes
这样我就不用找人攀谈了
and keep me from having to mingle.
我被男伴甩了
My date ditched me.
你要是现在撇下我  那就很失礼了
So if you abandon me now, that would be very rude.
高跟鞋真要命
These heels are killing me.
摸摸看  这些水泡
Feel that. Feel that blister.
我有女朋友了
Hey, I...I have a girlfriend.
要没有才奇怪呢
I'd be surprised if you didn't.
你的男伴为什么要甩了你
Why'd your date ditch you?
说来很丢人
Mmm. Very scandalous.
怎么回事
What happened?
碰个杯
Clink glasses with me.
我虽然个子小  但很能喝
I'm petite, but I can hold my liquor.
看出来了
Obviously.
我一喝醉了就...
When I do get drunk, though...
就怎样
What then?
就脱衣服
I get undressed.
你呢
What about you?
你喝醉了会怎样
What are you like when you get drunk?
-不太好看  -好看不顶用
- It's not pretty. - Pretty's overrated.
我反而喜欢不堪的场面
I like it when things get a little bit ugly.
我要是工作到很晚
When I work late nights,
他们就让我住酒店
they let me stay at the hotel
我就不用开车回家了
so I don't have to drive home.
这张给你
This one is yours.
1121号房间
Room 1121.
先生
Sir?
在这儿
In here.
您找我吗
You wanted to see me?
我要你找一个人
I need you to locate somebody.
谁
Who?
我太太
My wife.
你有办法做到吗
Do you have a way of doing that?
有  先生
I do, sir.
我认识一个人  失踪人口部的...
I know a guy in missing persons...
她没有失踪  我只是
She's not missing. I just...
不知道她现在在哪里
don't know where she is at the moment.
我信任他
I trust him.
我们可以私下办
We can do this off the books.
很好
Good.
我这就去办
I'll get on it right away.
来嘛  再说个笑话
Come on. Give us another one.
不  我告诉你
No. I'll tell you why.
我妈妈以前总让我多笑笑
Because my mother always used to tell me to smile more.
总让我抓狂  她会说  "克莱尔
Always drove me crazy. She'd say, "Claire",
你怎么总是愁容满面
"Why have you that scowl all the time?
你笑起来的样子美多了"
You look so much more beautiful when you smile."
我们从来没真正聊过
It was never a real conversation.
她从来不会问我  "你感觉怎么样"
There was never, "Oh, what do you feel?"
或者"你在想什么"
Or "What are you thinking?"
只要我看上去漂亮幸福
Just so long as I looked beautiful and happy.
她只关心这个
That's all she cared about.
那你是希望我问你
So you want me to ask you
你在想什么  感觉怎么样
what you're thinking and feeling?
一直问
All the time.
其实我也挺好奇你的想法和感觉
I actually do wanna know what you're thinking and feeling.
-我真可悲啊  -是啊  不如你先说
- How sad am I? - Yes, so tell me first.
-什么  -你先告诉我
- What? - Tell me first.
-我还是去穿衣服吧  -什么  为什么
- I think I'd better get dressed. - What? Why?
因为...
Uh, because...
我约了朋友来
I've got friends coming over,
作为主人  总得穿件衣服
and as a host, I should probably wear clothes.
-真的吗  -对
- Really? - Yeah.
-那是为什么  -你懂的
- Why do you do that? - Well, you know.
-比较妥当  -差不多
- It's proper? - Kind of.
该死
Oh, fuck.
还以为你不来了呢
Thought you might have bailed.
坐吧
Sit down.
伏特加还是威士忌
Vodka or whiskey?
你喝吧
Uh, you go ahead.
拜托  你在楼下装乖就算了  在这儿不用啊
Come on. You can be a good boy downstairs, not up here.
真的  我不用
Seriously, I'm good.
威士忌吧
Whiskey, I think.
你的好消息是什么
So what's your good news?
我想知道我们在庆祝什么
I wanna know what we're celebrating.
你的男伴为什么甩了你
Why did your, uh... why did your date ditch you?
-我先问的  -我在楼下就问了
- I asked you first. - I did, downstairs.
他在国会工作
He works on the Hill.
工作人员之类的
Some staffer or something.
我也不清楚  可能就是个普通职员
I don't know. I think he's a glorified gofer.
一个朋友介绍的
A friend set me up with him.
我说他今晚可以过来陪我
So I said he should come tonight, keep me company.
但他只想和我闲扯
But all he wanted to do was schmooze.
我就带他去了女盥洗室
So I brought him into the women's bathroom,
跟他说他是个混蛋
told him he was being an asshole.
他反过来说我幼稚
He told me I was being childish.
我就扇了他一巴掌
So I slapped him.
你扇他耳光
You slapped him?
没错  脸上五道红指印
Yeah. Big red hand mark right across his face.
我想他怕被人看见丢脸
I think he was embarrassed to be seen by the Schmoozerati.
所以就走了
So he left.
这是我最后一次
And that is the last time
和戴国旗胸针上班的人约会了
I go on a date with a guy who wears a flag pin to work.
我也是其中之一
I'm one of those guys who wears a flag pin to work.
我们也不是在约会啊
This isn't really a date, is it?
我真的不该来这儿的
I really shouldn't be here.
这样才有趣
That's what makes it fun.
告诉我你的好消息  我们为什么干杯
Tell me your good news. I wanna know what we're toasting to.
我们为你干杯
Let's toast to you.
我就是你的好消息  好啊  干杯
I'm your good news? Okay, I'll toast to that.
你这是...
What are you...
我不想在《先驱报》报社等
I didn't wanna wait at the Herald.
我本来想给你打电话  但是
I was gonna call you, but...
我今晚能住你家吗
Can I stay at your place tonight?
和我住
Uh, stay with me?
我睡沙发就行
Well, just on your couch
就一两晚
for a night or two.
为什么
Uh, why?
家里待不下去
I can't be in my apartment.
-发生了什么  -没有
- Did something happen? - No. I...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
佐伊
Zoe.
走吧
Come on.
采访几点开始
What time is the interview?
差一刻八点  我在一旁守着
Quarter to 8:00. I'll be with him.
彼得现在在哪
And where's Peter now?
你真想知道细节吗
Are you sure you want the details?
告诉我进展是否顺利就行
Just tell me, is it going well?
还没有新消息
Hasn't been any updates.
如果进展顺利  你准备好了吗
But if it does go well, you'll be ready?
我早准备好了
I'm ready. I've been ready. I'm ready.
-还有事吗  -我们从没下过国际象棋吧
- Anything else? - We never played chess before, have we?
我不会
I don't know how.
要不要我教你
You want me to teach you?
我该去休息了
I should really get some rest.
为明早养精蓄锐
Be fresh for the morning.
好  下次再说
Yeah, another time.
7点45  调幅1160  WZPZ
1160, WZPZ, 7:45.
晚安
Good night.
我讨厌不知情
I hate being kept in the dark.
焦急等待
Waiting.
胡乱猜测
Speculating.
无能为力
Useless.
来吧  和我跳支舞
Oh, come on! Let's dance.
没事的
It's not a big deal.
-来跳舞嘛  -不要
- Come on, let's do it. - No.
拜托了  我真的不跳
No, please, I can't. Not now.
来吧
Come on.
这房子真不错
This is really nice.
要喝点什么吗  水还是果汁
Do you want anything? Water? Juice?
不用了  谢谢
No, thanks. I'm good.
床让给你  我睡沙发吧
Uh, you can have the bed. I'll sleep on the couch.
不用不用
No. No.
没关系
It's fine.
拜托了  卢卡斯  让我睡沙发吧
Please, Lucas, let me sleep on the couch.
不然我良心不安
I'll feel bad.
好吧
All right.
-需要帮忙吗  -我来吧
- Can I help? - I got it.
那个
So,
你不想谈就不要勉强
you know, we don't have to talk if you don't want to.
不过我们
But I haven't seen you in, like,
六个月没见了
six months.
除了我上回喝醉了跟踪你
Except for when I drunkenly stalked you at your...
-嗯  -挺可爱的
- Right. - That was kind of adorable.
应该说是发疯或是可悲
It was either psychotic or sad.
哪里可爱
Not adorable.
真的挺可爱
Yes, it was.
能把枕头递给我吗
Can you hand me that pillow?
为什么要离开公寓
So, why do you need to get out of your apartment?
感觉太小
It just felt small.
不会比我这儿还小
Well, it can't be smaller than my place.
不  不是面积小  是...
No. I don't mean size. I mean...
我感觉像一只困兽
I felt trapped.
好像我并不住在那里
Like I was in a place that I didn't actually live.
你能明白吗
Does that make any sense?
或许吧
I guess.
好了
Okay.
搞定
There you go.
你什么时候起床
Um, anytime you need to get up?
我用手机定闹钟就好
Um, I'll just set an alarm on my phone.
好吧  想看电视就看
All right. Well, feel free to watch TV.
再大声我都睡得着
I can sleep through anything.
谢谢你  卢卡斯
Hey, thank you, Lucas.
就剩这么点了
Hey, that's the last of it.
那可得好好利用
Better make it count, then.
喝光
Drink up.
你觉得我面熟吗
Do I look familiar to you?
面熟吗  不觉得
Familiar? No.
-脸和身体  -没印象
- My face? My body? - No.
那我的声音呢
How about my voice?
我们以前...
Have we...
没有
No.
不  我只是好奇
No. I was just wondering
你是不是偏爱蓝眼睛的褐发女人
if you had a thing for brunettes with blue eyes.
你去哪  回来
Hey, where you going? Come back here.
我想看得清楚点
I wanna see you better.
该死  天亮了
Shit. The sun's up?
亮了有一会儿了
Has been for a while.
-该死  几点了  -7点15了
- Oh, fuck. What time is it? - 7:15.
该死  我半小时后有个采访
Fuck. I have an interview in half an hour.
-别做了  -不行  必须得做
- Skip it. - I can't. I gotta do it.
你可以到中午再退房
You can keep the room till noon.
-你好  -我在你家楼下
- Hello? - I'm at your building.
前台一直打电话  但没人接
The front desk keeps calling up, but there's no answer.
-我不在那儿  -那我去找你  你在哪
- I'm not there. - Then I'll come to you. Where are you?
我在  在帕克-海默尔酒店
I'm... I'm at the Park Highmore hotel.
你还好吗  好像喝醉了
Are you okay? You sound drunk.
就是  嗯嗯  我没事
It was, uh... yeah. Yeah. I'm... I'm all right.
-你还有个采访  -我知道
- You have the interview. - I know!
你又喝酒了吗  彼得
Have you been drinking, Peter?
什么  没有  我只是想在这儿住一晚
Uh, what? No. Um, I just decided to spend the night here.
你在哪个房间
What room are you in?
11  1121号
11, uh... 1121.
待在那儿  我马上过来
Stay there. I'm coming right now.
天哪  彼得  怎么了  你喝醉了
Jesus, Peter. What happened? You're drunk.
-我没事  -我都闻到酒味了
- I'm fine. - I can smell it on you.
好吧  我是喝了一两杯
Okay, I had a drink or two.
没喝多
It was nothing crazy.
我们不能接受采访了
We can't do this interview.
我很清醒  应付得来的
I'm sober. I can handle it.
你话都说不清楚了
You're slurring your words.
我很好
I'm good.
还是取消吧
I think we should cancel.
我要接受采访
I'm gonna do the interview.
给我谈话要点就行
Just give me the talking points.
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉  我
Sorry. I...
没关系
It's all right.
沙发床里有个弹簧还是什么  我的背
The couch had a spring in it or something, and my back...
没事
No.
没关系
It's all right.
我不介意
I don't mind.
先生  我朋友来消息了
Sir, I heard from my friend.
失踪人口那个
Missing persons.
然后呢
And?
-她在纽约  -哪家酒店
- She's in New York. - What hotel?
没住酒店  先生
Not a hotel, sir.
她没自己住
So she's not alone.
是的  先生
No, sir.
亚当・嘉乐威吗
Adam Galloway?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
还有别的消息
I have more information.
我不想知道
I don't need to know.
调到调幅1160
Turn on 1160 A.M.
他正在竞选接替吉姆・马修斯做宾州州长
He's running to fill Jim Matthews' old post as Governor of Pennsylvania.
罗素竞选州长
很高兴你能来作客  先生
Glad to have you with us, sir.
我很高兴  吉姆
It's good to be here, Jim.
-这是马克  -抱歉  马克
- It's mark. - Sorry. Right. Mark.
没事  议员先生
That's okay, Congressman.
这么早难免有点犯糊涂
It happens all the time this early in the morning.
议员先生  流域法案
So, Congressman, the watershed act.
是啊  我为此感到羞愧
Yes. Uh, I'm ashamed of the...
不  我并不感到羞愧  不对
well, I'm not ashamed. That's not the right, um...
我很失望  因为
I'm disappointed, um, because, you know,
流...
the water...
就是  其实我想说的是...
It's, um... it's... actually, what I'd like to discuss is...
大家都知道我们州的...
we all know that natural gas...
天然气一直...在发展
that it's... it's a growing... uh, in our state...
它是经济的...
it's a... it's a big part of, um...
重要部分...就目前情况而言
economically, the way things are going.
我想说...想宣布
And I'd like to say... to announce...
就某些方面
in terms of, um...
你熟悉开采条例吗
Are you familiar with drilling regulations...
开放使用和限制使用的
permitted use versus conditional use?
我们是在说流域法案吗
Are we still talking about the watershed?
不  开采  天然气
No. Drilling. Natural gas.
先生  你之前支持加大监管啊
Sir, you supported increased regulation.
不  我...
Well, no. I... I...
可能看起来是这样  但...
it may have looked that way, but, uh,
事实上  其实我是赞成少些...
in fact, to be clear, I'm for less...
监管的
regulation.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
但流域法案中  清楚表明...
In the watershed bill, the language clearly stated...
但它没通过
It didn't pass.
没错  这就是我的问题
Well, right. That's what I'm asking about.
-什么意思  -它为什么没通过
- What about it? - Why it didn't pass?
我刚说了
I just said.
不  先生  我认为你没有
No, sir. I don't think you did.
它就是没通过
It just didn't.
先生  三天前  你预测说...
Sir, three days ago, you predicted...
我在说他妈的天然气
I'm talking about fucking natural gas.
对不起
I'm sorry.
议员先生  我得问你一个问题
Congressman, I have to ask you a question,
可能会有点唐突
and it may come across as indelicate,
你是不是喝醉了
but are you drunk right now?
什么  没有  没有  我没事  没事
What? No. No. I'm fine. I'm fine.
我只是...很累
I'm just... I'm really tired, you know?
佐伊  你要我提供些更好的新闻...
我忙了几周的竞选活动了
I've been on the campaign trail for a few weeks now,
议员先生
Congressman?
议员先生  议员先生
Congressman? Congressman?
都是我的错
It's my fault.
我不该让你做的
I shouldn't have let you.
我完蛋了
I'm fucked.
听着  我们先帮你醒酒
Okay. Listen. We sober you up.
再尽快发表个声明
We'll make some kind of announcement as soon as possible.
说什么都没用了
There's nothing I can say.
我们会想出对策的
We'll figure this out.
起来
Come on.
去冲个澡
You're gonna take a shower.
来吧
Come on.
这就对了  来吧
There you go. Come on.
有多糟
How bad is it?
关键要看
It all depends on whether
主流媒体会不会报道
it gets picked up by the mainstream press.
-那要告诉总统吗  -不用  先别说
- Well, shall I fill in the president? - No. Hold off on that.
我要和彼得谈一谈  协调一下他的竞选
I need to speak to Peter, coordinate with his campaign.
完事了第一个打给你
You'll be the first call I make.
弗兰克  先别挂
Frank, before you go,
我早上收到一封电邮
I got an e-mail this morning.
斯坦福改变了决定
Stanford reversed their decision.
太好了
That's wonderful.
教务长说吉莉安・科尔跟他打了招呼
The Provo said Gillian Cole reached out to him.
我上网查了  她为克莱尔工作
I googled her. She works for Claire.
-谢谢你  -不用谢我
- Thank you. - No reason to thank me.
鲁本高兴极了
Ruben was just ecstatic.
我都不知道该怎么报答你
I don't know how I'm gonna repay you.
你儿子高兴就够了
The fact that your son is happy is more than enough.
-彼得那边你随时通知我  -当然
- You'll keep me posted on Peter? - You bet.
好的
Okay.
先生
Hey, boss.
-你还和他在一块吗  -是的
- Are you still with him? - Yeah.
-他在冲澡  -情况怎么样
- He's taking a shower. - How're we looking?
十分钟前佐伊・巴恩斯在网上曝光
Zoe Barnes posted ten minutes ago.
《纽约时报》官网已经报道了
It's already on the New York times web site.
这孩子完了
The kid is done.
让南茜安排跟副总统会面
Have Nancy set up a meeting with the Vice President.
-最好今天  -就去办
- Today if possible. - Will do.
留心彼得  他该做的都做了
And keep an eye on Peter. He's done his duty.
-让他重新振作起来  -没问题
- Let's get him back on his feet. - You got it.
现在轮到吉姆・马修斯出场了
And now Jim Matthews comes to the fore,
不过他自己还不知道呢
though he doesn't know it yet.
他会在他心爱的宾州找到慰藉
He will find solace in his beloved Pennsylvania,
而彼得・罗素则没那么幸运
though Peter Russo will find solace nowhere.
十秒钟就足以摧毁一个人的雄心
It only takes ten seconds to crush a man's ambitions.
我得小心保护自己的雄心
I need to take care that I protect mine.
彼得
Peter.
Peter!
彼得
Peter?
翻译  猪猪
翻译  waterlike
翻译  sakura
翻译  噎死青春
翻译  小蟹
翻译  泽川
翻译  ~某人
翻译  木月
翻译  小饭
翻译  风吹日落
时间轴  chance-coco
顾问  老杜
后期  饿得慌
校对  草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第一季  第十集
人人影视倾情奉献